{
    "id": "b15ad428c3bf4057a574839f5151691d",
    "title": "Reported Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane said that she was quite sure that she ........................... in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will return",
                "would return",
                "returned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f620774b95fb40b4af341e05836f3601"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ............................... his friend good bye.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bid",
                "bade",
                "bidden"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "741a40375c0440de82d15e819708d687"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother ................................ me home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "welcome",
                "welcoming",
                "welcomed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c14256bba1064963a86ed6438e50055a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ................................ me for my help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thank",
                "thanked",
                "thanking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1cd1c764bb3424b9f0f56d03187d505"
        },
        {
            "question": "He expressed his hope that I ............................... well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ff4924f6feb423cb323ce05b93cfce3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused ................................... not guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "plead",
                "pleaded",
                "pleading"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54118c229d1146af8876219554577ec9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I advised him ............................... his parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to obey",
                "that he obey"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e144ef5a7ca42a3ba61e492e39f1607"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother asked her daughter if she knew where the keys ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67e8b03b5c8545aa8d22c11d8664a306"
        },
        {
            "question": "James asked me if I ................................... spare some money for him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9bb9bdba7724e9c96a532ae00d097cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Voila asked Rosalind where she ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was going",
                "am going",
                "has going"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c97cd464a6240acbd9a6dd87a06bcbb"
        }
    ]
}